{
  "grades": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "grade": "1st"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "grade": "2nd"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "grade": "3rd"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "grade": "4th"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "grade": "5th"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "grade": "6th"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "grade": "7th"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "grade": "8th"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "grade": "9th"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "grade": "10th"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "grade": "11th"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "grade": "12th"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "grade": "Freshman"
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "aboutMe": "Edit your profile to update your about me section!",
      "email": "edwin.moz@parent.com",
      "firstName": "edwin",
      "lastName": "moz",
      "userTypeId": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "aboutMe": "Edit your profile to update your about me section!",
      "email": "alba.moz@parent.com",
      "firstName": "alba",
      "lastName": "moz",
      "userTypeId": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "aboutMe": "Edit your profile to update your about me section!",
      "email": "edwins.student@student.com",
      "firstName": "edwins",
      "lastName": "student",
      "studentId": 1,
      "userTypeId": 2,
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "userTypes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "description": "Parent",
      "type": "isParent"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "description": "Student",
      "type": "isStudent"
    }
  ],
  "students": [
    {
      "firstName": "edwins",
      "lastName": "student",
      "gradeId": 3,
      "userId": 1,
      "studentCode": 3315,
      "id": 1
    }
  ],
  "studentWorksheets": [
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "studentId": 1,
      "worksheetId": 4,
      "id": 1,
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is the earth shape?",
          "answer": "Flat",
          "hint": "If you know you know",
          "studentAnswer": "flat"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What year was the moon landing?",
          "answer": "Haven't been there yet",
          "hint": "The more you know",
          "studentAnswer": "2019"
        }
      ],
      "isComplete": true,
      "isApproved": true
    },
    {
      "userId": 1,
      "studentId": 1,
      "worksheetId": 2,
      "id": 2,
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "2-1",
          "answer": "1",
          "hint": "No",
          "studentAnswer": "1"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "3-2",
          "answer": "1",
          "hint": "No",
          "studentAnswer": "1"
        }
      ],
      "isComplete": true,
      "isApproved": false
    }
  ],
  "subjects": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Mathematics"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Science"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "History"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "name": "English"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "name": "Computer Science"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "name": "Physical Education"
    }
  ],
  "worksheets": [
    {
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "2+2",
          "answer": "4",
          "hint": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "3+3",
          "answer": "6",
          "hint": "No"
        }
      ],
      "title": "Addition",
      "gradeId": 2,
      "subjectId": 1,
      "userId": 2,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "2-1",
          "answer": "1",
          "hint": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "3-2",
          "answer": "1",
          "hint": "No"
        }
      ],
      "title": "Subtraction",
      "gradeId": 2,
      "subjectId": 1,
      "userId": 2,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "2x2",
          "answer": "4",
          "hint": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "3x3",
          "answer": "9",
          "hint": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "4x4",
          "answer": "16",
          "hint": "No"
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "5x5",
          "answer": "25",
          "hint": "No"
        }
      ],
      "title": "Multiply",
      "gradeId": 3,
      "subjectId": 1,
      "userId": 2,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "questionAndAnswers": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is the earth shape?",
          "answer": "Flat",
          "hint": "If you know you know"
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What year was the moon landing?",
          "answer": "Haven't been there yet",
          "hint": "The more you know"
        }
      ],
      "title": "Science",
      "gradeId": 1,
      "subjectId": 2,
      "userId": 1,
      "id": 4
    }
  ]
}